review came back.
The project lead was very impressed with the quality of the code he committed.
code was not documented well enough.
And that did not make her happy.
As we all know, good documentation is essential.
A well-written code base up until a certain level documents itself.
Let's say by using good method names.
variable names and so on.
But that alone is rarely enough.
Let's see how CoPilot can help with this.
There's actually a documenting command built into code.
I've shown it to you when we first took a lap around Copacabana.
Let me open the order handler.
There we go.
There's not enough documentation here yet.
So let's just...
Moscow
document.
It suggests documentation for the get orders async method.
acceptance
and it automatically did the same.
the other methods.
And that is how easy it is to add documentation to your code.
Don't forget to validate that the